

- Bashundhara R/A, Dhaka,1229
 Bangladesh
- +8801868984364
- md.faisal3@northsouth.edu
- https://www.linkedin.com/in/md-faisal-ahmed-
- https://github.com/mdfaisalahmed02:
- https://cool-lokum-b4bfaf.netlify.app/

SUMMERY

I am innovative and forward-thinking to achieve the goal. I have good communication skills and have experience in teamwork. I have experience on Machine learning and web development as well as content writing. I love to travel different places in Bangladesh and love to take photos.

SKILLS

- Python and Django
- Node Js and Express Js
- Machine Learning
- Seo Expert And Content creator
- HTML, CSS, BOOTSRTAP JAVASCRIPT
- WordPress developer
- Graphic Designer,
- Microsoft excel, Powerpoint, canva pro

MD FAISAL AHMED

EXPERIENCE

September 2020 - Current

Seo Expert and Content Creator | Own

- Read and understand technical texts on the different articles and writing content.
- Collaborated with network specialists to resolve security breaches.
- · Improved web design and usability
- Managed online content using best practices in SEO to improve search rankings.
- Produced and updated website to facilitate daily visitors.
- Partnered with technical teams to align designs with hosting and site performance capabilities.

May 2019 - Current

Wordpress Designer | Own

- It was my own website where I worked for amazon affiliate marketing
- I am working on theme customization and different plug in
- Understood functional requirements and adapted design work accordingly.

EXTRA-CURRICULAR ACTIVITIES

June 2019 - Current

Sub-Committee | North South University Social Services Club

- Developed ongoing programs using good team communication and collaboration.
- Demonstrated consistent hard work and dedication to achieve results and improve operations.

EDUCATION

2022

Bachelor of Science | Computer Science and Engineering North South University | Dhaka, Bangladesh Current Cgpa: - 3.08

2017

Higher School Certificate | Science Government Science College| Dhaka, Bangladesh Gpa:-4.92

2015

Secondary School Certificate | Science Lalpur Nazrul Islam High School | Cumilla, Bangladesh Gpa:- 5.00